pilship.com 2018-11-16

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers Pacific International Lines' treatment of personally identifiable information that Pacific International Lines collects when you are on the Pacific International Lines site. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Pacific International Lines does not own or control, or to people that Pacific International Lines does not employ or manage.

Pacific International Lines collects personally identifiable information when you fill in the feedback form available for your use on our site. When you choose to fill in the Pacific International Lines feedback form, we ask for your name and e-mail address. Pacific International Lines uses the personally identifiable information you supply on our feedback form to respond to your inquiries only. Pacific International Lines also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address (see below) and the page you requested. Pacific International Lines uses this information for statistical purposes only.

Pacific International Lines will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Pacific International Lines will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when we have your consent to share the information or we respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

Pacific International Lines may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

If you have questions or suggestions please send an email to [general@sgp.pilship.com](mailto:general@sgp.pilship.com)

The Pacific International Lines web site contains links to other web sites; however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

When your web browser or email application requests a web page or email from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This is called your computer's "IP address." (IP stands for "Internet protocol.") For most users accessing the Internet from a dial-up Internet service provider (ISP), the IP address will be different every time you log on.

Pacific International Lines receives IP addresses from all users because your browser automatically reports this information each time you view a web page. IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including to:

  * Diagnose service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP. 

  * Send the most appropriate advertising based on geographic area or information derived from your IP address. Many IP addresses are commonly associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major corporations in specific regions or localities. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.

  * Estimate the total number of users visiting Pacific International Lines from specific countries or regions of the world. When a Pacific International Lines web page is requested and viewed, that request is logged on our servers with information including the IP address of the computer that requested the page. 

Our website contains hyperlinks to social media (also known as “social plugins”) operated by third Parties. The functionality of these social plugins where in particular the transfer of information and user data is not activated by visiting our website, is only by clicking the hyperlinks. 

Once you click on any of these links, the plugin of the respective social media tools will be activated and your browser will establish a direct connection with the server of this social media tool.

  * Facebook (provided by Facebook, Inc.) to identify users logged in to Facebook for the purpose of sharing content on Facebook (only when you are logged in to Facebook when visiting our website and only when clicking the Facebook button)

  * WeChat (Provided by Tencent International Pte. Ltd) to identify users logged in to WeChat for the purpose of sharing web message content reflecting from their smartphone (only when you are logged in to WeChat when visiting our website and only when clicking the WeChat button with the QR code to logon)

We have implemented appropriate organizational and technical security measures to protect your personal data. We store personal data on servers with limited access located in secured facilities, and our security measures are evaluated on an ongoing basis. The servers are protected by anti-virus software and firewalls.

For questions regarding the Collection, Processing or Use of Personal data relating to you or in case of a withdrawal of an informed consent regarding the disclosure, correction , deletion of data. Please contact us at

Email: [dpo@sgp.pilship.com](mailto:dpo@sgp.pilship.com)
